christmaslightsetc.com 2017-01-04

# Support

At Christmas Lights, Etc., the privacy and protection of your personal and financial information is very important to us. That's why we've created this privacy statement which fully describes our information gathering and dissemination practices. It's the best way we can demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy.

**Christmas Lights, Etc. uses your personal information for the following purposes:**

  * Building your ChristmasLightsEtc.com account  

  * Facilitating the ordering process  

  * Personalizing delivery of the content contained within our website  

  * Those who communicate with Christmas Lights Etc and supply us with contact information may receive future communications by email, direct mail, or telephone. If you do not wish to receive correspondence from Christmas Lights Etc, you can [contact us](http://www.christmaslightsetc.com/ContactUs.asp) with a request to be removed from our mailing list.

**Use of Your Information**

When you register with our site, we ask for your name and e-mail address. Then we ask you to create a password to allow you secure access. We use this to:

  * Process and track your orders
  * Send order and shipping confirmation emails

If you choose to receive emails about special offers, we will also:

  * Send catalogs you have requested and mailings that may be of interest to you, provided you have not requested otherwise
  * Send exclusive email offers of new product announcements and special promotions, provided you have not opted out of receiving these notifications

We may also use information from your account based on your site visits to generate statistics and aggregate reports for internal use, which may be shown to affiliates, subsidiaries, licensees, successors, and partners. These statistics and aggregate reports will not contain any personally identifiable information and your identity will be kept anonymous. Certain confidential information--such as passwords and credit card numbers-- is not disclosed in any of these reports.

If you purchase a product or service from Christmas Lights, Etc., the information you give--such as your credit card number, purchase information, and contact information--is provided to the banking merchant. Details regarding the purchase are supplied to the distributor or vendor partner. This is necessary to complete the transaction.

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties, except to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested service, under circumstances required by law, or--in limited cases--to our business partners as outlined in this policy.

You will not be contacted directly by any third party as a result of your relationship with Christmas Lights, Etc. unless you have given us permission to do so. Any business partners with whom we share your information will be subject to confidentiality restrictions preventing them from sharing your personal information with others.

**Security Precautions**

Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

When you transmit credit card information to complete a purchase or verify data, we always transmit that credit card number in an encrypted format. We use the industry standard 128-bit SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.

In addition to our encryption standards, your ChristmasLightsEtc.com account information is password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personal information. Please do not disclose your password to anyone. Always remember to sign out of your ChristmasLightsEtc.com account and close your browser window when your transactions are complete. This helps keep your account safe.

While we strive to protect your personal information, no data transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be 100% secure. Thus, ChristmasLightsEtc.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information during transmission to or from our site, and you submit information to us at your own risk. However, we do our best to ensure the highest level of security on our systems.

**Cookies**

We are committed to providing personalized products and services to you. In order to do so, ChristmasLightsEtc.com uses cookies to store a unique identifier. A cookie is defined as a small amount of text that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. If your browser is configured to enable cookies, then your browser adds the text sent to the appropriate file.

ChristmasLightsEtc.com uses cookies to tell us that you have visited our site before, to automatically display information you have requested, and to keep track of the items in your cart (shopping cart). They are used to help us simplify and enhance your shopping experience. A cookie may also be used to tailor ad content both on the site you are visiting as well as other sites within that network that you may visit in the future.

Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the Internet. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html or third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

**Disclaimer**

Ultimately, you are held responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Always be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

Christmas Lights, Etc. SHALL NOT BE HELD RESPONSIBLE FOR DAMAGE OR LOSS OF ANY KIND DUE TO ANY PRODUCTS OR SERVICES PURCHASED AT Christmas Lights, Etc. OUR MAXIMUM LIABILITY TO YOU IS THE AMOUNT YOU PAID FOR THE PRODUCT. WE DO NOT NECESSARILY ENDORSE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES MENTIONED AT Christmas, Lights Etc. NEITHER DO WE MAKE ANY WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE), ABOUT THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES IN OUR STORE OR THE ACCURACY OF OUR PRODUCT AND SERVICES LISTINGS. Christmas Lights, Etc. DISCLAIMS ALL RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY DAMAGES CAUSED BY VIRUSES CONTAINED AT OR WITHIN Christmas Lights, Etc. SITES OR WITHIN ANY ELECTRONIC FILES SENT FROM Christmas Lights, Etc. SITES.

This site contains links to other sites. Christmas Lights, Etc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other Web sites.

**Trademarks and Copyrights**

Christmas Lights, Etc., ChristmasLightsEtc.com and the Christmas Lights, Etc. logo are trademarks or registered trademarks of Christmas Lights, Etc. Everything on this Web site is Copyrighted, 2000-2010, Christmas Lights, Etc., unless otherwise specified. All Rights Reserved. All other product names and company logos are the trademarks of their respective owners.

**Pricing**

Prices listed or quoted from Christmas Lights, Etc. are subject to change without notice and are subject to availability.

**Errors and Omissions**

Christmas Lights, Etc. works hard to ensure the accuracy of the product information in our store. However, we are not responsible for typographical errors or technical inaccuracies.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

If we make changes to our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Web site for you to review.

**FAQ questions**

**How private is my personal information?**

We may share member information in order to provide you with a more integrated and customized member experience. Your information will only be shared with trusted banking merchants, distributors, and/or vendor partners in order to facilitate our services to you.

**How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?**

You may opt-out from receiving our emails by following the instructions on any commercial email you receive from us. You may also opt-out buy using our [opt-out form](http://www.christmaslightsetc.com//pages/Email-OptOut.htm).

Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping. If you have any issues, you can also [contact us](http://www.christmaslightsetc.com/ContactUs.asp).

We use any information you provide us only to enhance your Web experience and enable us to better serve you.
